<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Timothy Ford</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Timothy Ford</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>HideOuts</title>
      <link>/project/hideouts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/hideouts/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HomeMetricsLLC</title>
      <link>/project/homemetrics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/homemetrics/</guid>
      <description> Co-Founder and CTO @ HomeMetricsLLC Hi, I am Timothy Ford, one of the founding members of HomeMetricsLLC. On top of leading the project development, I also work heavily on the HomeMetrics Android App (Native Development in Java) (on the Play Store soon!) as well as our backend API (Python and FastAPI hosted on GCP).
Awards/Achievments  Braun Inventor Award 2nd in South Dakota Giant Vision Business Competition 3rd in USD i2i Business Plan Competition  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Website</title>
      <link>/project/personalsite/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/personalsite/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MinneMUDAC Fall 2019</title>
      <link>/project/mudac/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/mudac/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SciKit-MultiLinear</title>
      <link>/project/scikit-multilinear/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/scikit-multilinear/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Undergraduate Research</title>
      <link>/project/undergradresearch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/undergradresearch/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Network Creation Models for Social Networks</title>
      <link>/post/networkcreation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/networkcreation/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In order to model how an epidemic spreads throughout a network, you first must have a network for the epidemic to travel through. The following is the beginning of a study on how to create social network models, models that represent the connections shared between people.
Erdos-Renyi (Binomial) Probability of an Edge For Erdos-Renyi graph, the probability of an edge is lamda/n where lambda is the mean value of edges for the network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cilantro Timelapse</title>
      <link>/post/cilantrostretch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/cilantrostretch/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m Back with Cilantro After recording my initial timelapse of basil, I learned many things that would make the process much easier than the first time. Since my cilantro decided to finally pop through the soil, I decided I would use this knowledge going forward to make yet another timelapse of seedlings, but this time much easier. The first thing I did was used what I thought was a higher quality camera (Logitech c270 I believe).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome and See Basil Grow</title>
      <link>/post/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/welcome/</guid>
      <description>Welcome Hello everyone, if you&amp;rsquo;re here, you probably have a reason to be here as well as a reason to be browsing through. If not, hi. You can learn about what I care about and do in the About page, see some of the projects I work on in Projects, and of course read about my thoughts in Posts. You can find me the places that matter most to me by following the links in the top right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A little bit about me...</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description> What I spend my time on: In no particular order, I put a lot of time into the following things:
 Mountain Biking Ultimate Frisbee Personal Projects School My amazing girlfriend  Experience Co-Founder/CTO - HomeMetricsLLC - June 2019 to Present Visit our website for more details about our product and ways to purchase. See the projects page for more details on what I personally have worked on.
Research Assistant - SDSM&amp;amp;T - August 2019 to Present Rapid City, SD Software Engineering Intern - Quarq - May 2019 to Present Spearfish, SD Teaching Assistant - SDSM&amp;amp;T - August 2018 to May 2019 Rapid City, SD Sales Representative - Best Buy - December 2016 to May 2019 Rapid City, SD Boulder, CO </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>